In this video, we'll focus on checking outputs generated by the system.
在本视频中，我们将重点关注系统生成的输出的检查。
Checking outputs before showing them to users can be important for ensuring the quality, relevance and safety of the responses provided to them or used in automation flows.
在向用户展示输出之前检查它们可能非常重要，以确保提供给他们或用于自动化流程的响应的质量、相关性和安全性。
We'll learn how to use the moderation API, but this time for outputs, and how to use additional prompts to the model to evaluate output quality before displaying them.
我们将学习如何使用审查 API，但这次是针对输出，并学习如何使用附加提示来评估输出质量，然后再显示它们。
So let's dive into the examples.
那么让我们深入到例子中。
We've already discussed the moderation API in the context of evaluating inputs.
我们已经在评估输入的上下文中讨论了审查 API。
Now let's revisit it in the context of checking outputs.
现在让我们在检查输出的上下文中重新审视它。
Moderation API can also be used to filter and moderate outputs generated by the system itself.
审查 API 也可以用于过滤和审查系统自动生成的输出。
And so here's an example.
这里是一个例子。
So here's a generated response to the user.
这是一个生成的用户响应。
And we're going to use the moderation API in the same way that we saw the earlier video.
我们将使用与之前视频中相同的方式来使用审查 API。
So let's see if this output is flagged.
让我们看看这个输出是否被标记。
And as you can see, this output is not flagged and has very low scores in all categories, which makes sense given the response.
正如您所看到的，这个输出没有被标记，并且在所有类别中得分非常低，这是合理的，考虑到响应。
In general, it can also be important to check the outputs.
总的来说，检查输出也非常重要。
For example, if you were creating a chatbot for sensitive audiences, you could use lower thresholds for flagging outputs.
例如，如果您正在为敏感受众创建聊天机器人，您可以使用更低的阈值来标记输出。
In general, if the moderation output indicates that the content is flagged, you can take appropriate actions such as responding with a fallback answer or generating a new response.
总的来说，如果审查输出表明内容已被标记，您可以采取适当的措施，例如回复一个备用答案或生成一个新的响应。
Note that as we improve the models, they also are becoming less and less likely to return some kind of harmful output.
请注意，随着我们改进模型，它们也越来越不太可能返回某种有害输出。
Another approach for checking outputs is to ask the model itself if the generated was satisfactory and if it follows a certain rubric that you define.
另一种检查输出的方法是询问模型本身是否满意生成的输出，并且是否遵循您定义的某些标准。
This can be done by providing the generated output as part of the input to the model and asking it to rate the quality of the output.
这可以通过将生成的输出作为模型输入的一部分，并要求其评估输出的质量来完成。
You can do this in various different ways.
您可以以各种不同的方式做到这一点。
So let's see an example.
那么让我们看一个例子。
So our system message is you are an assistant that evaluates whether customer service agent responses sufficiently answer customer questions and also validates that all the facts the assistant cites from the product information are correct.
因此，我们的系统消息是您是一个助手，评估客户服务代理的响应是否足够回答客户问题，并验证助手从产品信息中引用的所有事实是否正确。
The product information and user and customer service agent messages will be delivered by three backticks.
产品信息和用户和客户服务代理消息将通过三个反引号传递。
Respond with a Y or N character with no punctuation.
回答一个没有标点符号的Y或N字符。
Y if the output sufficiently answers the question and the response correctly uses product information and no otherwise.
如果输出足够回答问题并且响应正确使用产品信息，则为Y，否则为N。
I'll put a single letter only.
我只会放一个字母。
And you could also use a chain of thought reasoning prompt for this.
您还可以为此使用一种思维链推理提示。
This might be a little bit difficult for the model to validate both in one step.
这可能对模型来说有点困难，因为需要在一步中验证两者。
So you could play around with this.
因此，您可以尝试一下。
You could also add some other kind of guidelines.
您还可以添加其他类型的指南。
You could ask give a rubric like a rubric for an exam or grading an essay.
您可以询问是否使用了友好的语气，符合我们的品牌指南的规定，并可能概述您的品牌指南，如果这对您非常重要。
You could use that kind of format and say does this use a friendly tone in line with our brand guidelines and maybe outline some of your brand guidelines if that's something that's very important to you.
您可以使用这种格式，例如考试的评分标准或论文的评分标准。
So let's add our customer message.
因此，让我们添加我们的客户消息。
So this is the initial message used to generate this response.
这是用于生成此响应的初始消息。
And then that's also paste in our product information.
然后将其粘贴到我们的产品信息中。
And so this is the product information we fetched in the previous step for all of the products mentioned in this message.
因此，这是我们在前一步中获取的所有提到的产品的产品信息。
And now we'll define our comparison.
现在我们将定义我们的比较。
So the customer message is the customer message, the product information and then the agent response, which is the response to the customer that we have from this previous cell.
因此，客户消息是客户消息，产品信息以及代理响应，即我们从此前的单元格中获得的对客户的响应。
So let's format this into a messages list and get the response from the model.
因此，让我们将其格式化为消息列表并从模型中获取响应。
So the model says, yes, the product information is correct and the question is answered sufficiently.
因此，模型表示，是的，产品信息是正确的，并且问题得到了充分回答。
Well, in general, for these kind of evaluation tasks, I also think it is better to use a more advanced model because they're just better at reasoning.
总的来说，对于这些类型的评估任务，我认为最好使用更高级的模型，因为它们更擅长推理。
So something like GPT-4.
所以像GPT-4这样的东西。
Let's try another example.
让我们再试一个例子。
So this response is life is like a box of chocolates.
因此，这个响应是生命就像一盒巧克力。
So let's add our message to do with the output checking.
因此，让我们添加与输出检查相关的消息。
And the model has determined that this does not sufficiently answer the question or use the retrieved information.
模型已确定这不能充分回答问题或使用检索到的信息。
This question, does it use the retrieved information correctly?
这个问题，它是否正确使用了检索到的信息？
This is a good prompt to use if you want to make sure that the model isn't hallucinating, which is making up things that aren't true.
如果您想确保模型没有产生幻觉（即编造不真实的事物），这是一个很好的提示。
And feel free to pause the video now and try some of your own customer messages, responses and adding product information to test how this works.
请随意暂停视频，尝试一些自己的客户消息、响应和添加产品信息，以测试它的工作原理。
So as you can see, the model can provide feedback on the quality of a generated output, and you can use this feedback to decide whether to present the output to the user or to generate a new response.
正如您所看到的，该模型可以提供有关生成输出质量的反馈，您可以使用此反馈来决定是否向用户呈现输出或生成新的响应。
You could even experiment with generating multiple model responses per user query and then having the model choose the best one to show the user.
您甚至可以尝试为每个用户查询生成多个模型响应，然后让模型选择最佳响应以向用户显示。
So there's lots of different things you could try.
因此，您可以尝试许多不同的事情。
In general, checking outputs using the moderation API is good practice, but while asking the model to evaluate its own output might be useful for immediate feedback to ensure the quality of responses in a very small number of cases.
总的来说，使用审核 API 检查输出是一个好的实践，但是要求模型评估自己的输出可能对于确保非常少量情况下响应质量的即时反馈是有用的。
I think it's probably unnecessary most of the time, especially if you're using a more advanced model like GPT-4.
我认为大多数情况下这可能是不必要的，特别是如果您正在使用像 GPT-4 这样更先进的模型。
I haven't actually seen many people do something like this in production.
实际上，我没有看到很多人在生产中做这样的事情。
You could also increase the latency and cost of your system because you'd have to wait for an additional call for the model, and that's also additional tokens.
您还可以增加系统的延迟和成本，因为您必须等待模型的额外调用，这也是额外的令牌。
If it's really important for your app or product that your error rate is 0.0000001%, then maybe you should try this approach.
如果您的应用程序或产品的错误率非常重要为 0.0000001%，那么也许您应该尝试这种方法。
But overall, I wouldn't really recommend that you do this in practice.
但总的来说，我不会真正建议您在实践中这样做。
In the next video, we're going to put together everything we've learned in the evaluate input section, process section and checking output section to build an end-to-end system.
在下一个视频中，我们将把我们在评估输入部分、处理部分和检查输出部分学到的所有内容组合起来，构建一个端到端的系统。
Thanks.
谢谢。